Because you are my brother.
因为你是我的兄弟。
Xiao Douzi knocked you out
小豆子把你打晕了
of course he should apologize to you.
他当然应该向你道歉。
However, you also feel uncomfortable riding it again.
然而，再次骑行时你也会感到不舒服。
You should apologize to him too.
你也应该向他道歉。
This problem started with me.
这个问题是从我开始的。
I also keep Xiao Douzi.
我还养着小豆子。
So I also have to apologize to both of you
所以我也必须向你们俩道歉
you're not normal
你不正常
if it's still not normal
如果还是不正常
I'll chase him away for you.
我会替你把他赶走。
I won't take you
我不会带你
believe it or not?
信不信由你？
Sis.
姐姐。
Sister-in-law.
嫂子。
Charm.
魅力。
Why is it here?
为什么会在这里？
I understand.
我明白。
Sis,
姐姐，
You and Mrs. Luo want to continue their relationship again.
你和罗太太想再次继续他们的关系。
Mei Kai dua kali
Mei Kai dua kali
humble.
谦逊的。
This time can't let Guan Qun know anymore.
这次不能再让管群知道了。
Truly.
确实。
Indeed, we met the forest after a long dry season.
确实，我们在经历了漫长的旱季之后才见到了森林。
Otherwise, why did her earring break too?
不然怎么她的耳环也断了？
You go. Go.
你去。去。
You just go busy.
你就去忙吧。
Sister.
姐姐。
Quickly return your earrings.
赶紧把耳环还回去。
So as not to be discovered by Luo Guanqun again.
以免再次被罗冠群发现。
First of all I want to know
首先我想知道
your specific action plan is still a plan
你的具体行动计划仍然是一个计划
we will move with the storm team
我们将与风暴队一起前进
save the kidnapped members first
先解救被绑架的成员
and also the workers
还有工人
then set the bomb
然后设置炸弹
destroy the counterfeit money factory.
摧毁假币工厂。
What is it?
它是什么？
Our plan is problematic.
我们的计划有问题。
I've asked.
我问过。
This factory continues production 24 hours,
这家工厂24小时持续生产，
at the same time, it still exists
同时，它仍然存在
teams of Japanese soldiers stood guard day and night.
一队队日本兵日夜站岗。
Want to enter from the main door
想从正门进入
that's very difficult.
那是非常困难的。
So, you underestimated Team Storm's combat power.
所以，你低估了风暴战队的战斗力。
Enough to face some unprepared Japanese troops.
足以面对一些毫无准备的日军。
Still many.
还是很多。
But don't forget,
但别忘了，
Shanghai-Xi section of the Military Police Headquarters
宪兵司令部沪西段
is 15 minutes from this factory
距离这家工厂 15 分钟路程
from this factory.
来自这家工厂。
Once the battle begins,
一旦战斗开始，
their help will be very fast.
他们的帮助会非常快。
If so, what is your suggestion?
如果是这样，您的建议是什么？
There is only one way
只有一种方法
say it.
说吧。
Every 8 p.m
每晚八点
office workers in this factory
这家工厂的办公室职员
and also night shift workers.
还有夜班工人。
Will change shifts.
会换班。
Apart from the workers
除了工人之外
Japanese troops
日军
will be guarded by two soldiers,
将由两名士兵看守，
others will also change shifts.
其他人也会换班。
So in this time
所以在这个时候
in the entire factory there were only two foremen
整个工厂只有两个工头
there are still 2 Japanese soldiers
还有2名日本兵
is when the defense is very weak.
就是防御非常薄弱的​​时候。
Correct.
正确的。
But this shift change won't take too long.
但这种转变不会花费太长时间。
20 minutes at most.
最多20分钟。
Twenty minutes.
20分钟。
In that case, we simply don't have time to deploy
在这种情况下，我们根本没有时间进行部署
and perform operations.
并执行操作。
However, if within these 20 minutes
然而，如果在这20分钟内
can reach the target,
能够达到目标，
I think we still have a chance of success.
我认为我们仍然有成功的机会。
You mean the right target?
你是说正确的目标吗？
Before the operation begins
手术开始前
we go into the factory,
我们走进工厂，
Look for the location of the money printing factory.
寻找印钞厂的位置。
Then, ask the Storm Team to get straight to the point.
然后，请 Storm 团队开门见山。
Before help arrives,
在救援到来之前，
we completed the mission.
我们完成了任务。
This factory
这家工厂
continuously producing for 24 hours
24小时连续生产
Apart from that, there is a team of Japanese soldiers
除此之外，还有一队日本兵
how do we get in
我们怎么进去
So,
所以，
You know I'm the one who takes care of general affairs,
你知道我是负责总务的人
Let's just say your luck is good.
只能说你的运气很好。
I've asked.
我问过。
Lunch and dinner at this factory.
午餐和晚餐在这家工厂。
By a restaurant in town
在镇上的一家餐馆旁边
the so-called restaurant opening restaurant.
所谓餐厅开餐厅。
Wait until the dining cart arrives at the factory
等到餐车到达工厂
the foreman will check all workers' certificates
工头会检查所有工人的证件
then a restaurant worker
然后是餐馆工作人员
bringing food into the factory,
把食物带进工厂，
one by one.
逐个。
What you mean is
你的意思是
we can disguise ourselves as restaurant employees.
我们可以将自己伪装成餐厅员工。
Correct
正确的
the scale of this restaurant is large
这家餐厅规模很大
there are lots of people
有很多人
its mobility is frequently used.
它的移动性经常被使用。
The foreman cannot possibly know everyone's face.
领班不可能认识每个人的脸。
As long as we make witnesses as one,...
只要我们作为一个见证人，...
Then the foreman will no longer be suspicious.
那么工头就不会再起疑心了。
But even if we enter the factory,
但即使我们进了工厂，
how can you find a counterfeit money factory?
如何找到假币工厂？
I'm considering it too.
我也在考虑。
We now have absolutely no clue.
我们现在完全没有任何线索。
Guoguo,
Guoguo,
try to think about it.
试着想一想。
The Japanese locked up workers and experts.
日本人关押了工人和专家。
But it must ensure their basic survival every day
但必须保证他们每天的基本生存
right, right?
是的是的？
Good.
好的。
The counterfeit money factory numbers 30 to 40 people.
假币工厂有30至40人。
Plus Japanese troops
再加上日军
how to prepare their food?
如何准备他们的食物？
I remember Guo Yun once said,
我记得郭云曾经说过，
they can eat buns every afternoon.
他们每天下午都可以吃包子。
My wife's memory is the best.
我老婆的记忆力是最好的。
Correct.
正确的。
Lunch, eat two packs of vegetables,
午餐，吃两包蔬菜，
the night of porridge and flower rolls.
粥和花卷之夜。
Once every week
每周一次
= Gemice = You can eat meat buns once at night
= Gemice = 晚上可以吃一次肉包子
This is the opening restaurant menu.
这是餐厅的开幕菜单。
I understand.
我明白。
The food they send to the military clothing factory,
他们送到军装厂的食物，
actually there are some,
实际上有一些，
sent to an underground counterfeit money factory
送到地下假币工厂
Correct.
正确的。
There must be someone
一定有人
send some of the food to a counterfeit money factory.
将一些食品送到假币工厂。
As long as we follow this guy,
只要我们跟着这个人，
we can find out the location of this counterfeit money factory.
我们可以查到这个假币工厂的位置。
This is a great way.
这是一个很好的方法。
Go down.
下去。
Give me the ring.
把戒指给我。
Remember that.
请记住这一点。
Do not speak.
不要说话。
After this operation is complete,
此操作完成后，
commander of the Military Police Soldiers
宪兵司令
will definitely do research on all of us.
肯定会对我们所有人进行研究。
Including everyone in the factory.
包括工厂里的所有人。
Will check one by one.
会一一核对。
We are some people disguised as delivery people
我们是一些伪装成送货员的人
the picture will definitely be painted.
这幅画肯定会被画出来。
Especially the two of us,
尤其是我们两个人，
frequent contact with Japanese people.
与日本人接触频繁。
So you have to pretend well
所以你要假装得很好
I saw today they eat meatloaf.
我今天看到他们吃肉饼。
These two big buckets were supposed to be for workers
这两个大桶本来是给工人用的
the two below,
下面两个，
should have been sent to a counterfeit money factory.
应该被送到假币工厂。
Your analysis is not wrong.
你的分析并没有错。
In this basket,
在这个篮子里，
supposedly for Japanese soldiers and foremen.
据说是为日本士兵和工头准备的。
How do we divide the tasks later?
后面的任务怎么划分呢？
You guys distribute buns to the workers outside.
你们给外面的工人分发包子。
I went to serve the Japanese and the foreman.
我去给日本人和工头服务。
I'm coming with you.
我跟你一起去。
Don't believe me.
别相信我。
Good.
好的。
No problem.
没问题。
Guoguo, help me look for a moment.
果果，帮我找一下。
Why is it so late today?
今天怎么这么晚？
Why have you just arrived?
你怎么才到？
Far
远的
Why is everyone foreign today?
为什么今天大家都是外国人？
Change people again.
又换人了。
You go ask the boss.
你去问问老板吧。
I see your emotions are not small.
我看你的情绪不小。
Of course.
当然。
Sending 50 minutes to you
发送50分钟给你
delivery to the city only a dozen minutes,
送货到市区只需十几分钟，
give me the same salary.
给我同样的工资。
If you don't have emotions,
如果你没有感情，
Have you brought your ID?
你带身份证了吗？
Stop it.
停下来。
Here.
这里。
Help me.
帮我。
Work quickly.
快点工作吧。
When we're finished, we'll go home quickly
结束后我们就快点回家
quickly dry or dissolve
快速干燥或溶解
your face comes out
你的脸出来了
have you finished looking?
你找完了吗？
Wait.
等待。
If you don't want to come,
如果你不想来的话
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
It's me.
这就是我。
At that time fighting with guests,
那时与客人打架，
made Boss Zhou angry.
惹周老板生气了。
Because I,
因为我，
because I.
因为我。
How is Boss Zhou?
周老板怎么样了？
I'm asking you.
我在问你。
Mute.
沉默的。
Can not hear?
听不见？
Boss Zhou recently married his second wife.
周老板最近娶了他的第二任妻子。
He married a second wife
他娶了第二任妻子
it's all money to exploit us
都是钱来剥削我们
in your opinion second family
在你看来第二个家庭
is he also part of us?
他也是我们的一部分吗？
You're a kid
你还是个孩子
It's finished?
都结束了？
Go with me.
跟我走。
Go away.
离开。
Go ahead.
前进。
Come on, come in quickly.
来吧，快点进来吧。
Fast.
快速地。
Hello, sir
你好先生
time to eat
吃的时候
here, here, lined up.
这里，这里，排队。
Here.
这里。
Here. Fast.
这里。快速地。
Go there!
去那里！
Fast!
快速地！
This.
这。
You guys pick this up
你们把这个拿起来
fast.
快速地。
Where is ours?
我们的在哪里？
Follow me.
跟我来。
Road.
路。
Kapten Matsumoto.
松本船长.
Dinner has arrived.
晚餐到了。
This.
这。
What are you eating today?
你今天吃什么？
I'm talking to him.
我正在和他说话。
Kapten Matsumoto.
松本船长.
He's mute.
他是哑巴。
Senior officers don't be angry.
高级官员不要生气。
That's it.
就是这样。
Let me introduce you, okay?
让我介绍一下你，好吗？
Today's dish is this white cut chicken.
今天的菜是这道白切鸡。
Boiled eggplant with oil.
用油煮茄子。
Shrimp fried in oil,
油里炸虾，
white grilled salty
白烤咸
Iga babi Hu Jiang
伊贺巴比胡江
and also mustard soup
还有芥末汤
these vegetables are delicious.
这些蔬菜很好吃。
Hurry up.
赶快。
Senior officers, eat slowly.
各位长官，慢慢吃吧。
I'll deliver the food first.
我先把食物送过来。
Stay cool.
保持冷静。
We will go back to the way it was before
我们会回到以前的样子
we will provide the best food for you.
我们将为您提供最好的食物。
Sir, very good.
先生，非常好。
Take good care of the chiefs.
好好照顾首领。
I accompanied him to deliver vegetables.
我陪他送菜。
No need, I'll go alone.
不用了，我一个人去。
Stupid!
愚蠢的！
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
No points?
没有积分？
Be careful.
当心。
Is the King okay?
国王还好吗？
Look at it.
看它。
Fast.
快速地。
I'm telling you.
我告诉你。
Give me eyes.
给我眼睛。
Hear not?
没听见吗？
Pak,
帕克,
Then I'll go first.
那我就先走了。
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Wait a minute
等一下
shrimp
虾
Good stuff.
好东西。
Shrimp.
虾。
Fall to the floor.
跌倒在地板上。
You...
你...
Eat it.
吃了它。
Thank you sir
谢谢你，先生
eat it
吃了它
Shrimp is good stuff.
虾是个好东西。
Shrimp must eat.
虾一定要吃。
Shrimp?
虾？
Very delicious.
非常美味。
Thank you, senior officer.
谢谢你，高级官员。
Wait!
等待！
This side street
这条小巷
go quickly!
快去！
Hear not?
没听见吗？
I'm afraid I won't be able to catch up.
我怕我追不上。
He did something to the tow truck.
他对拖车做了什么。
Who's that?
那是谁？
Go, hurry. We'll get caught.
走吧，快点。我们会被抓住的。
Help me
帮我
I beg you.
我求求你。
If we don't leave, we'll be found out.
如果我们不离开，就会被发现。
He's seen us.
他见过我们。
If you don't help him, you will be found out.
如果你不帮助他，你就会被发现。
Foreman Sun had already gone far away.
孙工头已经走远了。
Thank you for helping me.
感谢你们对我的帮助。
Earlier if I was caught,
如果我早点被抓住的话
I will definitely die.
我一定会死。
Now you will die too, understand?
现在你也会死，明白吗？
Wait.
等待。
He works in a uniform factory.
他在一家制服工厂工作。
If you don't kill him,
如果你不杀他
he's going to leak us!
他会泄露我们的秘密！
I... I won't tell you guys!
我……我不告诉你们！
I just want to steal things to fill my stomach.
我只是想偷点东西填饱肚子而已。
I have absolutely no idea what you guys are doing.
我完全不知道你们在做什么。
You wild child!
你这个野孩子！
Ruining our big plans.
破坏我们的大计划。
No.
不。
Wait.
等待。
You climb the wall
你爬墙
to steal food to fill the stomach.
偷食物来填饱肚子。
Correct.
正确的。
Our dinner is just a bowl of porridge, a loaf of bread.
我们的晚餐只是一碗粥，一条面包。
Not full at all.
一点也不满。
Where do you want to steal it?
你想偷到哪里去？
foreman Sun
孙工头
The stroller has an iron bucket
婴儿车有铁桶
there is bread in it
里面有面包
how do you know?
你怎么知道？
In foreman Sun's iron bucket are there buns?
孙工头的铁桶里有包子吗？
I stole it once.
我偷过一次。
Where
在哪里
once before
以前有过一次
I work in a barren place
我在荒芜的地方工作
I saw foreman Sun pushing a trolley
我看见孙工头推着小车
past there.
过去那里。
I'm thinking
我在想
what is on the iron barrel?
铁桶上有什么？
is there food in it?
里面有食物吗？
So I followed him
于是我就跟着他
up to the warehouse door
直到仓库门口
foreman Sun opened the warehouse door and entered
孙工头打开仓库门走了进去
the stroller stopped there
婴儿车停在那里
I took the opportunity to get closer
我趁机靠近
to open the iron box.
打开铁盒子。
Inside it turned out to be full of meat buns.
里面竟然装满了肉包子。
I took two then ran.
我拿了两个然后就跑了。
Don't smell it again.
别再闻了。
Remember which warehouse?
还记得哪个仓库吗？
Still remember.
还记得。
Is warehouse number 23
仓库号是23号吗
Do you know the way?
你认识路吗？
Know.
知道。
Take us away.
带我们走吧。
Otherwise, I will kill you!
不然我就杀了你！
Good.
好的。
Road.
路。
What way?
有什么办法？
Over there.
在那边。
Good.
好的。
Possible.
可能的。
Why did he come back again?
他怎么又回来了？
Look at this bucket,
看看这个桶，
we didn't bring it here, right?
我们没有把它带到这里，对吗？
This means he has finished delivering the food.
这意味着他已经送完饭了。
What he took was yesterday's bucket
他拿的是昨天的桶
street
街道
Road.
路。
Here.
这里。
This is warehouse number 23.
这是23号仓库。
When I came,
我来的时候，
here it is guarded by Japanese soldiers.
这里有日本兵把守。
I took advantage of them going to the toilet.
我趁他们去厕所的时候。
just got the buns
刚拿到包子
are you sure?
你确定吗？
Confident.
自信的。
Good.
好的。
Hurry home.
快点回家吧。
It's time to share the food.
是时候分享食物了。
I guess.
我猜。
You must be fighting Japan, right?
你一定是在和日本作战吧？
Stop talking nonsense!
别废话了！
Still have.
还有。
Remember, okay?
记住，好吗？
Don't tell anyone
不要告诉任何人
can't tell anyone else.
不能告诉别人。
Was it just that I didn't say one word?
难道只是我没说一句话吗？
I am also an opponent of Japan.
我也是日本的反对者。
You ask him.
你问他。
Aren't you afraid he'll betray us?
你就不怕他背叛我们吗？
One day if I'm betrayed,
有一天，如果我被背叛，
then it must not be him.
那么一定不是他。
The counterfeit money factory is definitely here.
假币工厂肯定就在这里。
But don't you find it strange?
但你不觉得奇怪吗？
This important place
这个重要的地方
not even the military police were there.
甚至宪兵也不在场。
It's also too quiet.
也太安静了。
I'll go take a look.
我去看看。
Now it's time to eat.
现在该吃饭了。
The Military Police must have delivered buns for them.
宪兵肯定给他们送了包子。
Because the buns were sent here,
因为包子是送到这里来的，
there's definitely no problem
绝对没问题
the time is almost here,
时间快到了，
go quickly
快去
Hello, senior officer.
你好，高级官员。
Thank you sir
谢谢你，先生
I am not going to
我不会
do you drive a car?
你开车吗？
Correct.
正确的。
I'm a car driver
我是一名汽车司机
How long have you been coming to the hotel?
您来酒店多久了？
Soon, one month more.
很快，又一个月了。
What about Mr. Zhou's legs?
周先生的腿呢？
What's that?
那是什么？
I heard last week
我上周听说
Boss Zhou you guys had a car accident.
周老板你们出车祸了。
His leg is broken.
他的腿断了。
How is the recovery going?
恢复情况如何？
It's much better.
好多了。
The food lately has been delicious.
最近的食物很美味。
Please convey my regards to him.
请转达我对他的问候。
Good, sir.
好的，先生。
Good.
好的。
Where are you two going?
你们两个要去哪里？
Shrimp on the floor is not clean
地板上的虾不干净
immediately after eating diarrhea.
饭后立即腹泻。
Pack your things
打包你的东西
get out of here quickly
快点离开这里
go go
走吧
everyone go!
大家走吧！
How
如何
The counterfeit money factory is in warehouse 23.
假币工厂位于23号仓库。
Do you have any new discoveries?
你有什么新发现吗？
To the left of the workshop entrance
车间入口左侧
there is a red button,
有一个红色按钮，
should have been an alarm.
应该是一个警报。
Factory producing weapons and materials for the Japanese army
为日军生产武器和物资的工厂
will set an alarm like this.
会设置这样的闹钟。
We have to think of a way
我们得想办法
so that the warning is not triggered.
以免触发警告。
Now there is still 1 hour
现在还有1个小时
there's still an hour.
还有一个小时。
We gather with the Storm Team first.
我们先和风暴队集合。
We will create a specific action plan
我们将制定具体的行动计划
according to the latest situation we have.
根据我们掌握的最新情况。
Good.
好的。
Director Jiang.
Director Jiang.
I'm Storm Team Leader, Tao Dachun.
我是暴风队队长陶大春。
Two!
二！
All members of the Storm Team...
风暴队的所有成员……
Listen to Director Jiang's instructions.
听姜主任的吩咐。
Director Jiang, you guys are great.
姜主任，你们太棒了。
Can sneak into Japanese factories
可以潜入日本工厂
These are all blessings
这些都是祝福
someone helped us get a labor certificate.
有人帮我们拿到了劳工证。
Who is that good?
谁这么好？
I can't tell you his name.
我不能告诉你他的名字。
I can only tell you.
我只能告诉你。
He is the one we saved
他是我们所救的人
people from the evil department
邪恶部门的人
code, 5 Red Hearts.
代码，5颗红心。
Understand.
理解。
This is Hong Tao Wu.
这是吴洪涛。
Hello, Captain Tao.
陶队长您好。
Still a girl
还是个女孩
great, great.
很棒很棒。
He is the Captain
他是队长
chairman of the Sixth Team of the Su and Zhejiang Action Committee.
苏浙行动委员会第六小组主席。
Liu Wuchang.
Liu Wuchang.
Two.
二。
This.
这。
He is...
他是...
I introduce myself
我自我介绍一下
chen Jia Ping
chen Jia Ping
a traitor.
叛徒。
Traitor?
叛徒？
This problem is long to tell.
这个问题说来话长。
But he is now on our side.
但他现在站在我们这边。
Two.
二。
Director Jiang.
Director Jiang.
I want to know right away
我想马上知道
division of factory buildings uniformly.
统一划分厂房。
To create a specific action plan.
制定具体的行动计划。
Good.
好的。
Please
请
have you heard clearly, right?
你听清楚了吧？
Already.
已经。
This operation,
这次操作，
there can be no mistakes in every procedure.
每道工序都不能有差错。
This time it's our mission
这次是我们的使命
can only succeed,
才能够成功，
cannot fail.
不能失败。
Good.
好的。
The time is almost here.
时间快到了。
Get ready to go
准备出发
Good.
好的。
You stay here,
你留在这里，
Why?
为什么？
Stay cool.
保持冷静。
I won't kill him
我不会杀他
after the operation is complete
操作完成后
I will let it go.
我会放手的。
I'm also not interested in participating in your actions.
我也没有兴趣参与你的行动。
Director Jiang?
Director Jiang?
Can let my wife stay here
可以让我妻子留在这里
accompany me to chat?
陪我聊天？
What do you think?
你怎么认为？
He must join in the action.
他必须加入行动。
Good.
好的。
My wife.
我的妻子。
Here.
这里。
Then I won't be able to protect you anymore.
那么我就无法再保护你了。
act,
行为，
you have to be careful.
你必须要小心。
Look at it.
看它。
They did this to me.
他们对我做了这样的事。
Work hard for them.
为他们努力工作。
Totally inappropriate.
完全不合适。
Bai Qian.
Bai Qian.
Until.
直到。
Have you remembered your movement task?
你还记得你的运动任务吗？
Already.
已经。
Later, when you act,
后来你行动的时候，
be careful
当心
far away!
离这很远！
Don't come forward.
别上前。
Before 8.15
8.15之前
Drive the car to the T-junction behind the military clothing factory
把车开到军装厂后面的丁字路口
Remember, you have to turn off the lights.
记住，你必须关灯。
Turn from the west.
从西转。
Avoiding help that might come.
避免可能到来的帮助。
Which may come.
这可能会到来。
Good.
好的。
Move.
移动。
See you later
回头见
why not let Chen Jiaping come along?
为什么不让陈家平一起去呢？
Japanese maybe
可能是日本人
already got PKT banknotes
已经拿到PKT纸币了
and it should be under this counterfeit money factory
应该是在这个假币工厂下面
our mission this time
我们这次的任务
not only destroying counterfeit money factories,
不仅摧毁假币工厂，
also took back the coins
还收回了金币
although Chen Jia Ping has helped us a lot
虽然陈家平帮了我们很多
but he's not our guy
但他不是我们的人
if he knew the news about the bronze version,...
如果他知道青铜版的消息的话……
Even to the point of leaking information to the Communist Party.
甚至到了向共产党泄露情报的地步。
That will have a big impact on our plans.
这将对我们的计划产生重大影响。
Already home.
已经到家了。
In front of the door there were 2 Japanese soldiers
门前有2个日本兵
and foreman Sun
和工头孙
other than the gatekeeper
除了看门人之外
in total there were ten Japanese soldiers.
总共有十名日本兵。
There were nine who left.
离开的有九人。
There should be one more person
应该还有一个人
Mrs. Agung smokes.
阿贡夫人抽烟。
Here.
这里。
Did you see the red alarm
你看到红色警报了吗
in that room?
在那个房间里？
Have seen it.
已经看过了。
Get rid of this guy first.
先解决掉这个家伙吧。
Go away.
离开。
Key
钥匙
Mr. Head,
海德先生，
This is a fake paper
这是一张假纸
but where did this guy go
但这家伙去哪儿了
where is the equipment?
设备在哪里？
There is a secret passage here.
这里有一条秘密通道。
You guys stand up first, don't move.
你们先站起来，别动。
I went down to see what was happening.
我下去看看发生了什么事。
Chief.
首席。
How
如何
the counterfeit money factory must have been transferred.
假币工厂肯定已经转移了。
The bottom part is clogged.
底部被堵塞。
Blocked.
被封锁。
Could it possibly explode?
有可能爆炸吗？
The counterfeit money factory must be underground.
假币工厂肯定是在地下的。
Otherwise we wouldn't find fake banknotes
不然我们就不会发现假钞了
It is just
这只是
Why?
为什么？
They suddenly moved.
他们突然动了。
Mr Director,
主任先生，
what are your plans now?
你现在有什么计划？
Disband first.
先解散吧
Road.
路。
Are you okay?
你还好吗？
How did you get out?
你怎么出去的？
I'll tell you later.
我待会儿告诉你。
The Military Police Squadron will arrive soon.
宪兵中队很快就会到达。
We definitely can't get out of the main door.
我们绝对不能走出大门。
So how?
又怎样？
Blow up the wall.
炸毁墙壁。
Hide.
隐藏。
Then ran outside
然后跑到外面
smash the wall and hide.
砸碎墙壁并躲起来。
Hide.
隐藏。
Come with me back.
跟我回去吧。
Fast!
快速地！
Hurry up.
赶快。
Road!
路！
Protect Director Jiang.
保护姜主任。
Split up, see you at the warehouse
分头行动，仓库见
See you at the warehouse
仓库见
go
去
Hurry up.
赶快。
We go.
我们去。
What does it mean?
这是什么意思？
I'm sorry.
对不起。
Even though you saved us
尽管你救了我们
I am very grateful to you
我非常感谢你
but you know too much.
但你知道的太多了。
If I want to betray you,
如果我想背叛你
I'll wait until now.
我会等到现在。
You count
你数数
I really will believe it
我真的会相信
are you just a common traitor?
你只是一个普通的叛徒吗？
You can lie to the left twin,
你可以对左边的双胞胎撒谎，
but you can't lie to me.
但你不能对我撒谎。
I really shouldn't have saved you.
我实在不该救你。
Which you shouldn't do too much.
你不应该做太多。
You shouldn't be involved in our operation.
你不应该参与我们的行动。
Nor should he marry Zuo Shuang Tao.
Nor should he marry Zuo Shuang Tao.
However, I don't regret it.
不过，我并不后悔。
For the woman I love,
为了我爱的女人，
whatever is appropriate.
任何适当的。
Don't know, Director Jiang.
不知道，姜主任。
For the woman you love,
为了你所爱的女人，
What can Miss Han Lu do?
韩露小姐能做什么？
Wait!
等待！
Do not move
不要动
You think we'll believe your bullshit?
你以为我们会相信你的鬼话吗？
How did Bai Qian die?
白浅是怎么死的？
Why would the Japanese know our plans?
为什么日本人会知道我们的计划？
If Chen Jiaping really wants to betray us
如果陈家平真的想背叛我们
why do you still want to help us?
为什么你还想帮助我们？
He just wants to save you.
他只是想救你。
Of course I just want to save my wife
当然我只是想救我的妻子
who wants to help bastards like you?
谁愿意帮助像你这样的混蛋？
According to you
照你说的
where is Director Jiang?
姜主任在哪儿？
You go ask him?
你去问他？
Why ask me?
为什么要问我？
Say no?
说不？
If you still don't say so
如果你还不这么说
believe it or not I will shoot you dead
不管你信不信我都会开枪打死你
lower the gun
放下枪
put the gun down.
把枪放下。
Let him go.
放了他。
Why?
为什么？
I believe him
我相信他
Do you believe Chen Jia Ping?
你相信陈家平吗？
He is a traitor,
他是一个叛徒，
I believe in the Left Twin.
我相信左双胞胎。
So I also trust the people he trusts
所以我也信任他信任的人
take Chen Jia Ping away
take Chen Jia Ping away
treat him well
善待他
don't interfere in our affairs anymore.
别再干涉我们的事情了。
Stay cool.
保持冷静。
There won't be a next time.
不会有下次了。
Do you know why
你知道为什么吗
won't let you join the final act?
不让你参加最后一幕吗？
Why
为什么
because of the CCP copper coins
因为中共铜币
very likely fell into the hands of the Japanese.
很有可能落入日本人手中。
At first he thought he could find it
起初他以为他能找到它
in a counterfeit money factory,
在假币工厂里，
however, he doesn't want you to know.
然而，他不想让你知道。
According to you,
照你说的，
Where has the counterfeit money factory been transferred to?
假币工厂转移到哪里了？
Now I also have no clue anymore.
现在我也没有任何线索了。
What is it?
它是什么？
Who are you really?
你到底是谁？
What? Who am I?
什么？我是谁？
Karena Jiang Zhaoguo
Karena Jiang Zhaoguo
have the same suspicions as me,
和我有同样的疑惑
just wanted to kill you.
只是想杀了你。
Is...
是...
Are you from over there?
你是那边人吗？
What's over here?
这里是什么？
Me
我
is your husband.
是你的丈夫。
You just need to remember this.
你只需要记住这一点。
I'm guessing you won't talk much either.
我猜你也不会多说话。
It's just that one day I was afraid.
只是有一天我害怕了。
You're not even my husband
你甚至不是我的丈夫
other?
其他？
I dare not guarantee
我不敢保证
but only this thing
但只有这个东西
I really promise
我真的答应
Tuan Jiang.
Tuan Jiang.
Here are the ice cubes and whiskey I prepared for you.
这是我为你准备的冰块和威士忌。
Thank You.
谢谢。
Mr. Jiang is really great
江老师真的很棒
he can find the location of our underground factory
他可以找到我们地下工厂的位置
I saw a great one
我看到了一个很棒的
it should be you
应该是你
Dahua hotel, my whereabouts were exposed.
大华酒店，我的行踪暴露。
Today,
今天，
I've planned this all
这一切都是我计划好的
in the end it was in vain.
最终还是徒劳。
I like to talk openly
我喜欢开诚布公地说话
talk openly like this.
像这样公开谈论。
Mr. Jiang can stay here temporarily.
江先生可以暂时留在这里。
Your daily needs
您的日常需求
we will prepare it for you.
我们将为您准备。
Oh yes
哦是的
In the room I have prepared a jacket for you.
房间里我给你准备了一件外套。
No need for a suit.
不需要西装。
This one...
这个...
Quite good.
相当不错。
One.
一。
I can drink.
我可以喝。
But that doesn't mean that after drinking your wine,
但这并不意味着喝完酒后
I will discuss cooperation with you.
我将与您洽谈合作。
Future problems,
未来的问题，
we can talk slowly.
我们可以慢慢聊。
However,
然而，
I want to ask Mr. Jiang something.
我想问江老师一些事情。
Say it.
说吧。
Where did this labor certificate come from?
这张劳工证哪里来的？
Faked?
伪造的？
We've checked.
我们已经查过了。
The labor certificate is genuine.
劳工证是真的。
In each acquaintance letter there must be a different number.
每封熟人信中都必须有不同的号码。
If you look at this number,
如果你看看这个数字，
we found
我们发现
that this labor certificate
这张劳工证
comes from Taihe commercial bank.
来自太和商业银行。
In Chongqing there are also our people.
在重庆也有我们的人。
We recently received information,
近期我们收到信息，
there was a military member named Hong Tao 5,
有一个军人叫洪涛5，
lurking inside Taihe Company.
潜伏在太和公司内部。
This labor certificate
这张劳工证
is a gift from Hong Tao Wu, right?
是吴洪涛送的礼物吧？
I don't know Taihe Company.
我不知道泰和公司。
Tuan Jiang,
Tuan Jiang,
At least we have respected you.
至少我们尊重过你。
I hope you will also give me an honor.
希望您也能给我一份荣誉。
Cooperation or not,
合作与否，
we can talk about it later.
我们可以稍后再讨论。
But this thing
但这件事
You have to give an account to me.
你得给我一个帐号。
If not,
如果不，
everyone will feel embarrassed.
每个人都会感到尴尬。
The counterfeit money factory has been transferred,
假币工厂已转移，
nothing worked.
没有任何效果。
We lost a lot of teams.
我们失去了很多球队。
I might be involved too.
我可能也会参与其中。
Besides that,
除此之外，
The Zuo twins are already doubting my identity.
左氏双胞胎已经开始怀疑我的身份了。
Wang Dapu, this person.
王大璞，这个人。
Financial expert, copper engraver.
金融专家、铜雕师。
Has participated in minting and issuing coins.
曾参与铸造和发行硬币。
True identity
真实身份
is a military spy with a wild goose code.
是一名带有大雁密码的军事间谍。
After stealing copper coins,
盗取铜币后，
fled to Shanghai.
逃往上海。
There is information that this person was captured by the Japanese.
有消息称此人被日本人俘虏。
If there is new information, contact the organization.
如果有新信息，请联系该组织。
Everything,
一切，
today we invite a special expert
今天我们请来了一位特别专家
to give a lecture to you
给你讲课
welcome
欢迎
good greetings to classmates
向同学们致以良好的问候